Abdelfattah Hamdi

Abdelfattah | in Abdelfattah | \square abdelfattah.hamdy234@gmail.com | \quare +201092148296

Summary

Graduated from the Faculty of Electronic Engineering with a passion for competitive programming and web development. Experienced in leadership roles with a strong proficiency in programming languages such as Python, JavaScript, and C++. Skilled in database management.

Work Experience

Instructor @AMITLearning

Nov 2022 - present

Instructor of full stack diploma offered by AMIT

Full stack developer @PulseHub

Nov 2022 - Nov 2023

- Part time full stack developer using React and Django frameworks

Software Engineer Internship @bld.ai

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022

- Building frontend and backend for websites using react and django frameworks
- learning more about github, gitflow, agile methodology and using trello for manage projects
- Working with a team of technical engineers

Summer Training @Information Technology Institute

Jul 2022 - Sep 2022

- Windows Administration
- Linux Administration
- Firewall Technology
- HTML/CSS/JS

Projects and Achievements

Web Site for PulseHub Company

PulseHub

Management system for PulseHub, a company aimed at automating their workflow and facilitating data sharing among users and clients.

Developed using Django and Django templates.

E-commerce website using React & Django Frameworks

GitHub-repo

An e-commerce application built with React and Django frameworks.

It features two main views: one for users to browse and purchase products,

leave reviews, and view order history, and another for administrators

to perform CRUD operations on products, users, and staff.

Clone Udemy Website using React

GitHub-demo

An educational project aimed at replicating

the user interface of the Udemy platform using React.

It includes the homepage and course pages

mimicking the layout and functionality of Udemy.

Implement most of data structures using C++

GitHub Repos

Implementation of various data structures in C++ for educational and practical purposes.

PROBLEM SOLVING

- More than 600 problems solved on Codeforces.
- More than 200 problems solved on Hackerrank.
- More than 50 problems solved on LeetCode.
- ECPC Finalist 2021.
- Top 3 in Menofia ECPC 2021.

EDUCATION

2019 - 2024 Bachelor's Degree at Faculty of electronic engineering in menouf (GPA: 3.8/4.0)

SKILLS

programming languages C, C++, MikroC, C#, JavaScript, Bash Script, Python and Java

SQL MSQL , MySql, SQLite and Oracle SQL

Frameworks ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, Django and REACT

DEV Tools Git/GitHub, Trello, Linux, Agile methodology and gitFlow architecture

Last updated: December 25, 2024